



## Summary

Motivational leader and organizational problem-solver with advanced supervisory, team building and customer service skills. Experience stepping into roles and quickly making positive changes to drive company success. Focused on using training, monitoring and morale-building techniques to maximize employee engagement and performance.

#### Skills

- Staff training and development
- Customer rapport
- Working collaboratively
- Excellent communication skills
- Friendly and outgoing

# **Education and Training**

Some College (No Degree)
Diablo Valley College
Pleasant Hill, CA,
Culinary Arts

## Experience

#### **Sloat Garden Centers**

Assistant Manager | Pleasant Hill, CA 01/2018 to Current

- Implement training processes for newly hired employees and supervised department leads.
- Organize schedules, workflows and shift coverage.
- Mentor staff to enhance skills and achieve daily targets, using hands-on and motivational leadership.
- Conduct job interviews, led employee performance evaluations with constructive feedback.
- Deliver seminars to groups of people in various venues.

#### **Sloat Garden Centers**

Manager | Danville, CA 02/2015 to 01/2018

- Collaborated with staff to maximize customer satisfaction, streamline procedures and improve bottom-line profitability.
- Answered customer questions regarding plant growing conditions and proper care.
- Planned gardens and beds with seasonal displays.

#### Sloat Garden Centers

Assistant Manager | Mill Valley, CA 02/2014 to 02/2015

- Greeted and encouraged feedback from customers to implement in-store operational changes.
- Trained employees on additional job positions to maintain coverage of roles at all times.
- Recruited and hired qualified candidates to fill open positions.

#### Sloat Garden Centers

Customer Service Associate | Danville, CA 03/2012 to 02/2014

- Welcomed customers, answered questions and offered to assist with choosing, locating and accessing products.
- Assisted with visual display maintenance, sign pricing and information changes and organization of garden center equipment.

### Costco

Customer Service | Santa Cruz, CA 08/2007 to 11/2011

- De-escalated problematic customer concerns, maintaining calm, friendly demeanor.
- Tracked inventory, conducted cycle counts and audits and resolved issues to maintain accurate records.
- Identified safety hazards and notified management to determine proper resolution of issues.